Papers of Morris K. Udall, 1920-1995
University of Arizona Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1961-1990
  - Legislative Assistant Files, 1961-1992
    - 95th Congress: HR 7530, Nursing Home Sprinkler Systems. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - 95th Congress: HR 7643, Federal Emergency Administration Act. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - 95th Congress: HR 7757, Indiana Dunes. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - 95th Congress: HR 7816, Public Energy Competition Act. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - 95th Congress: HR 8021, Forest and Range Land Research. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - 95th Congress: HR 8099, Ak Chin Indian Water Rights. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - 95th Congress: HR 8202, Amendment-Federal Election Campaign Act (1971). 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - 95th Congress: HR 8397, Papago Tribal Land. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - 95th Congress: HR 8444, Energy Act. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - 95th Congress: HR 9141, Savings and Loan Disclosure 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 22)
    - 95th Congress: HR 9282, Congressional Pay Increase. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 23)
    - 95th Congress: HR 9694, Whistleblowers Bill. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 24)
    - 95th Congress: HR 9784, World Food Conference. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 25)
    - 95th Congress: HR 9953, Family Newspaper Tax Credits. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 26)
    - 95th Congress: HR 10058, National Education Opportunities Act, 1977. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 27)
    - 95th Congress: HCR 649, Nazi March. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 28)
    - 95th Congress: HJR 702, D.C. Representation. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 29)
    - 95th Congress: HR 936, Bottle Bill. 1977-1978 (Box 205, Folder 30-38)
    - 95th Congress: HR 4089, Indian Tax Amendments. 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - 95th Congress: HR 7916, Public Energy Competition Act. 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - 95th Congress: HR 10936, Amendment-Erisa (Employee Retirement Income Security Act). 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - 95th Congress: HR 11104, Tribal Community College Grants. 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - 95th Congress: HR 11240, Social Security Payment Increase. 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - 95th Congress: HR 11280, Civil Service Reform. 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 6-13)
    - 95th Congress: HR 11280, Civil Service Reform (cont.). 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 1-9)
    - 95th Congress: HR 11581, Vehicles for Illegal Transportation. 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - 95th Congress: HR 11629, Solar Energy Technology. 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - 95th Congress: HR 12344, Salt River-Pima-Maricopa Boundary Modification. 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - 95th Congress: HR 13372, Hunting and Migratory Birds. 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - 95th Congress: HR 13471, Patagonia Corp. 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - 95th Congress: HR 13584, Boy Scouts. 1977-1978 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - 96th Congress: Udall Sponsored Small Business Acts. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - 96th Congress: HJR 159, Commission on Presidential Nominations. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - 96th Congress: HR 1, Partial Public Financing. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 3-4)
    - 96th Congress: HR 39, Alaska Lands. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 5-6)
    - 96th Congress: HR 1825, Archaeological Protection. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - 96th Congress: HR 1885, BIA and Indian Health Services Retirement. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - 96th Congress: HR 1770, Preservation of Local Independent Newspapers. 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 9-14)
    - 96th Congress: HR 2770, Newspaper Bill. 1979-1980 (Box 209, Folder 1-19)
    - 97th Congress: HR 2770, Newspaper Bill (cont.). 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 1-7)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3227, National Educational Opportunities Act, 1979. 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3777, Franking Privilege. 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4778, Amendment Clayton Act-Oil Companies Monopolies. 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4872, Competition Review Act. 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 11-12)
    - 97th Congress: HR 6098, Competition Review. 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 13-15)
    - 97th Congress: HR 9484, Udall Newspaper Bill. 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - 96th Congress: HR 7640, Papago Water Rights. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - 96th Congress: HR 8494, Lobby Disclosure. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - 96th Congress: Budget-Fiscal Year 1981, Merit Sustain Cuts. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - 96th Congress: Hunt Commission on Presidential Nominating Process. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - 96h Congress: Udall-Obey Emergency Tax Cut Act, 1981. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 21-22)
    - 96th Congress: Competition Review Act. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 23)
    - 96h Congress: Voting Record. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 24)
    - 96th Congress: Domestic Content Bill. 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 25)
    - 97th Congress: HCR 178, Veto of Federal Trade Commission Rule. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - 97th Congress: HCR 195, Federal Reserve Board Appointments. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - 97th Congress: HJR 208, D.C. Sexual Assault Reform Act. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - 97th Congress: HJR 341, Alaska National Gas Transportation Act. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - 97th Congress: HJR 360, Federal Reserve Rescind Growth Rate Target. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - 97th Congress: H Res 3566, Foreign Aide Authorization. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - 97th Congress: H Res 4144, Emergency and Water Appropriations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - 97th Congress: SJ Res 58, Balanced Budget Amendments. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - 97th Congress: HR 58, Sunset Review Ac t. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - 97th Congress: HR 181, Social Security Minimum Benefits. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - 97th Congress: HR 1638, Lacey Act Amendments. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - 97th Congress: HR 2120, Product Liability. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - 97th Congress: HR 2330, Nuclear Regulatory Commission. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - 97th Congress: HR 2349, Fair Representation Act. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - 97th Congress: HR 2828, Municipal Revenue Bond Financing. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3112, Voting Rights Act Extension. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 16-17)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3356, Earthquake Hazards Reduction Act. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3423, Veterans Training and Business. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3462, Department of Justice Authorization. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3480, Legal Services Corporation. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3496, Sale Representation Protection Act. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 22)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3499, Veteran Health Care. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 23)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3517, Virgin Islands Immigrations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 24)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4034, HUD, Independent Agencies Appropriations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 25)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4035, Interior Appropriations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 26)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4053, Savings Bonds. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 27)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4144, Energy and Rates Appropriations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 28)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4164, Newspaper Bill. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 29-33)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4169, Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Appropriations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 34)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4242, Tax Cut of 1981. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 35)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4327, Immigrations Amendments of 1981. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 36)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4331, Social Security Benefits. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 37)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4363, Southern Arizona Water Rights Settlement Act. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 38)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4560, Labor, Health, and Human Services, Education Appropriations. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 39)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4563, Papago Water Rights Bill. 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 40)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4563, Papago Water Rights Bill (cont.). 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 1-2)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4935, Securities/Commodities Bankruptcy. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5118, Papago Water Rights Bill. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 4-17)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5135, Moratorium/Depository Regulations Reform. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5214, Products Liability Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - 97th Congress: HR 6037, Resource Conservation and Recovery Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - 97th Congress: HR 7640, Papago Water Rights Bill. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - 97th Congress: Obey/Udall Budget Plan. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - 97th Congress: Miller Budget Plan. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - 97th Congress: Budget. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 24)
    - 97th Congress: HJR 521, Foreign Affairs-Nuclear Freeze. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 25)
    - 97th Congress: H Res 521, Romanian Immigration Quotes. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 26)
    - 97th Congress: H Res 6457, Health Research Exterior. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 27)
    - 97th Congress: S 1224, Franking Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 28)
    - 97th Congress: Air Traffic Control. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 29)
    - 97th Congress: HR 746, Regulatory Procedures Act of 1982. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 30-31)
    - 97th Congress: HR 1146, San Carlos Indian Water Storage Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 32)
    - 97th Congress: HR 1524, Amend IRS Code-Invert Tax Credit. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 33)
    - 97th Congress: HR 2329, Cherokee, Chickasaw and Choctaw Claim. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 34)
    - 97th Congress: HR 3481, Pretrial Service Act of 1981. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 35)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4374, International Ocean Commerce Transportation. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 36)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4481, Justice Assistance Act of 1981. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 37)
    - 97th Congress: HR 4709, Prompt Payment Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 38)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5038, Federal Employees Health Benefits. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 39)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5133, Domestic Content (Automobiles). 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 40)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5203, Insecticide, Fungicide and Rodenticide. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 41)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5320, Job Training Partnership Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 42)
    - 97th Congress: HR 5540, Defense Industrial Base Revitalization Act. 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 43)
    - 98th Congress: HR 6294, Single Family Emergency Housing. 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 44)
    - 98th Congress: HR 6450, Bicentenary ERA Commemoration. 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 45)
    - 98th Congress: HR 6563, Supplemental Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 46)
    - 98th Congress: HR 6956, HUD/Independent Agencies. 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 47)
    - 98th Congress: HR 7044, Postal Service Investigation and Enforcement Authorization. 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 48)
    - 98th Congress: Agriculture Arizona District 2. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - 98th Congress: Agriculture-Pecan. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - 98th Congress: Budget Fiscal Year 1984. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - 98th Congress: Democratic Caucus. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - 98th Congress: Federal Aviation Administration. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - 98th Congress: Yuma Crossing. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - 98th Congress: HCR 40, Nutrition Program. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - 98th Congress: HCR 91, First Concurrent Resolution on the Budget. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 8-9)
    - 98th Congress: HCR 113, MX Missile Funding Fiscal Year 1983. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - 98th Congress: HCR 126, Truman Birthday. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 13, Nuclear Freeze. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - 98th Congress: HJR, 165, Extend Housing Project. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - 97th Congress: HJR 308, Public Debt Limit Increase. 1981-1982 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 338, Veto Override of Chicago Desegregation. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 353, Destruction of Korean Civilian Airliner. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 364, Authorizing U.S. Forces in Lebanon. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - 98th Congress: HJR, 368, Continuing Appropriation. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 402, U.S. Armed Forces in Grenada. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 19)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 403, Continuing Resolution Fiscal Year 1984. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 20)
    - 98th Congress: HJR 413, Continuing Resolution Fiscal Year 1984. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 21)
    - 98th Congress: SCR 7, Hayden, Carl. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 22)
    - 98th Congress: S 450, Mail Order Consumer Protection. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 23)
    - 98th Congress: S 602, Radio Martil Cuba. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - 98th Congress: S 675, Defense Department Conference Report. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1, Housing and Recovery Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - 98th Congress: HR 5, Ocean and Coastal Resource Block Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 27)
    - 98th Congress: HR 10, National Development Investment Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - 98th Congress: HR 20, Establishment Select Committee Staff. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 29)
    - 98th Congress: HR 58, Intelligence Committee Staff. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 30)
    - 98th Congress: HR 127, Committee Funding Resolution. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 31)
    - 98th Congress: HR 200, Contempt of Congress/Rita LaVele (Superfund). 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - 98th Congress: HR 254, Ethics Investigation. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 33)
    - 98th Congress: HR 265/266, Reprimands of Studds and Crane. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 34)
    - 98th Congress: HR 427, Gay Rights. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 35)
    - 98th Congress: HR 622, Death Benefit for Federal Firefighters & Police Officers. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 36)
    - 98th Congress: HR 656, Federal Employees Health Benefits. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 37)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1036, Community Renewal Employment Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 38)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1043, Federal Contact for Small Business. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 39)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1976, Elimination of Jones Act Exemption. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 40)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1183, Tax Equity Act of 1983. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 41)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1190, Emergency Agriculture Credit Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 42)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1234, Domestic Content. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 43)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1242, Boggs Bulk Cargo Bill. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 44)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1271, El Salvador Certificates. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 45)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1296, Payment In Kind Tax. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 46)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1310, Emergency Math and Science. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 47)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1398, Energy Conservation Daylight Savings. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 48)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1416, SEC Authorization. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 49)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1590, Emergency Commodity Distribution. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 50)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1616, Plant Closings Notifications and Consultation. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 51)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1646, Railroad Retirement Solvency Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 52)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1707, National Transportation. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 53)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1718, Emergency Supplemental Appropriations, 1983. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 54)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1870, Vietnam Vets Medal. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 55)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1900, Social Security/Universal Coverage. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 56-58)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1904, Child Abuse. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 59)
    - 98th Congress: HR 1983, Emergency Housing Assistance. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 60)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2062, National Marine Sanctuary. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 61)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2065, NASA Authorization. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 62)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2066, National Science Federation. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 63)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2077, Physicians Comparability Bill. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 64-65)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2112, Defense Production Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 66)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2148, Follow Through Program. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 67)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2173, Contract Services for Drug Dependent Offender. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 68)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2174, Federal Anti-Tampering Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 69)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2175, Justice Assistance Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 70)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2207, Emergency School Aid Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 71)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2230, U.S. Civil Rights Commission Exterior. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 72)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2230, Financial Interest & Syndication Rule. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 73)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2350, Health Research Extension Act. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 74)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2355, Vietnam Veterans Job Training. 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 75)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2357, Congressional Award Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2498, Confessional Advisory Board-Boxing. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2587, Energy Department. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2602, Customs. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2668, Consumer Product Safety. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2681, SEC Awards. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2714, Agriculture Productivity Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2773, Critical Agriculture Materials. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2755, FCC Authorization Act 1983. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2758, Federal Insecticide, Fungicide and Rodentcide. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2760, Intelligence Authorization Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2769, Caribbean Basin. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2780, State and Local Fiscal Assistance Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2807, Meals for Older Americans. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2867, Hazardous Waste Control & Enforcement Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2915, State Department Authorization. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2936, Board of Vets Appeals. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2943, The Close Up Fund/Washington Workshop Fund. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2948, Veterans Mortgage Assistance. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2957, Internal Recovery and Financial Stability Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2968, Intelligence Authority Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2972, Military Construct Authority. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - 98th Congress: HR 2973, Repeal of Interest and Dividend Tax. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3020, Small Business Authority Bill. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3021, Health Care for the Unemployed. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3044, Atlantic Salmon Compact. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3069, 1983 Supplemental Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 27)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3117/5888, Economic Equality Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 28)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3132, Energy and Water Development Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 29)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3133, HUD/Independent Agencies Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 30-31)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3135, Conference Report. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 32-33)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3222, Conference on State, Commerce, Justice Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 34-35)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3223, Agriculture Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 36)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3231, Export Administration Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 37)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3263, Military Construction Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3323, Washington Workshops. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 39)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3329, Transportation Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 40-41)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3354, National Child enforcement Act of 1983. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 42)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3363, International Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 43-44)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3385, Dairy/Tobacco Subsidies. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 45)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3385, Cotton Producers. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 46)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3391, Trade Adjustment Assistance. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 47)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3398, Tariff Amendments. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 48)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3409, Federal Supplemental Compensation Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 49)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3415, D.C. Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 50-51)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3520, Rehabilitation Act Amendments. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 52)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3564, Wheat and Grain Programs. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 53)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3648, Amtrak Improvement Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 54)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3649. National Health Service Corps. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 55)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3655, Retirement Age for DC Judges. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 56)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3706, Martin Luther King Day. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 57)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3862, Outer Continental Shelf. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 58)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3871, Federal Employee Pay Cut. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 59)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3913, Labor, Health and Human Services, Education Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 60)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3929, Federal Supplemental Compensation Act. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 61)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3932, Home Rule Act Amendments. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 62)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3958, Water Resources Development Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 63)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3959, Supplemental Appropriations Fiscal Year 1984. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 64-65)
    - 98th Congress: HR 3962, Export Administration Extension. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 66)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4091, School Lunch and Child Nutrition. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 67)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4102, Universal Telephone Service. 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 68)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4139, Treasury and Postal Service Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4169, Omnibus Reconciliation Act. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4185, Defense Appropriations. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4196, Dairy Surplus Reduction. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - 98th Congress: HR 4201, Methaqualone Prescriptions. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - 98th Congress: HR 6071, Trademark Counterfeiting Act. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - 98th Congress: Budget. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 7-13)
    - 98th Congress: Citrus. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - 98th Congress: Immigrations. 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 15)